{
 "data": [
    {
      "question": "______ Heathrow Airport is the biggest international airport in the world.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "In 2003 Thomas graduated from _______ University of Essex.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Use \"the\": when you are about to make it clear which person or thing you mean\n- Do not use \" the\": with words for institutions such as school, prison, college, university, church when you are talking about them in a general way\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mercedes announced ______ 20% profit for the first half of the year.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- A: used in some phrases that say how much of something there is: a profit of, a few, a great deal of...",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I've booked you a room at ______ Grand. It's the best hotel in the city.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Use \"the\": with words for institutions when you are talking about a particular one",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sally always goes for a walk in ______ St. John's Park on Sunday afternoons.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Normally, Proper Noun doesn't take any",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Andrew lives on _______ Bradwell Road. It's a very fashionable part of town.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport\n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ Prado Museum in Spain is one of the best museums in the world.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Use \"the\": with words for institutions when you are talking about a particular one",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The history of ______ Winchester Cathedral in England goes back to the 7th century.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport \n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "We went to ______ Petronelli's to celebrate Margaret's birthday. It's the best restaurant in town.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Do not use \"the\" with the name of a place, for example a street, town, country, or airport\n- Do not use \"a/an\" when you mention a specific person or thing\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The home of ______ European Parliament is in Strasbourg.",
      "a": "a",
      "b": "an",
      "c": "the",
      "d": "-",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- TheÂ European Parliament",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "1",
      "subcategorylv2": "13",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ] 
}